One Band. One Dream. One Summer.
Satisfaction is a comedy, music, romance film directed by Joan Freeman.
When a young rock group called The Mystery gets its first gig at a
club, it's an opportunity to see what life is all about.
Fresh out of high school, the rockers are hired by an exclusive
beach resort thanks to a faded '60s songwriter.
There, they meet with romance and adventure.
But street-smart lead singer Jennie Lee faces a dilemma:
pursue her budding career or finish high school.
Jennie Lee, played by Justine Bateman.
Martin Falcon, played by Liam Neeson.
Mooch, played by Trini Alvarado.
Nickie, played by Scott Coffey.
Billy, played by Britta Phillips.
Daryle, played by Julia Roberts.
Satisfaction (also titled Girls of Summer) is a 1988 American comedy-drama film
directed by Joan Freeman and starring Justine Bateman and Liam Neeson.
Primarily known today as Julia Roberts' first credited big-screen role, Satisfaction is also one
of the few theatrical productions by either Aaron Spelling or the NBC network.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.